[{"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "Your life is extraordinary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "URNETT: Of course.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "But that's the best way, isn't it?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "She didn't really mean it in the most flattering way, didn't she?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, right now it's the writing.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Old.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "How do you feel about being described as a living legend?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Lifetime achievement.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "How important was it for you to lead a sort of healthy, active life given that you came from two parents who were both alcoholics, weren't they?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "No, I never made up my mind -- I never said that to myself, I just wasn't that interested in, you know -- and I always felt there was something that was going to happen.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Did that sort of send you the message right, I was not going to abuse myself that way?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is that what it was?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "We didn't have the money.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, not -- you know, I don't know what would've happened, but that was when I was bitten by the theatrical bug at UCLA.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "And without that, it would never have happened?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Perform at a black-tie dinner party.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "But this was a guy who hired you and a group to come perform, right?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "And he didn't want you to ever say who he was?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "And you never have, right?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "And you did all those things, didn't you?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "But you've met up with this guy, didn't you?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "You have to be ready.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do you think if you live a dream properly and you have this game plan luck comes your way?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "URNETT: No, I don't.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "You really don't think so?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No, we worked very well together.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Doesn't that create even more competition?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Rivals and all that?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "And when you -- when you met him, he had eight children already?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "And you then had three more children?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "So it's now eleven?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, I think towards the end, I -- it's really too personal, but we also parted as friends.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "And why didn't it work out, the marriage, do you think, when you look back on it?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "ORGAN: He's 20 years younger than you, yes?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Not bad at all.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "It's not bad, is it?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "That's an interesting question.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What have you learned about who you need to be around?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Is that an integral part of your life?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I don't have any boring friends.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "I mean as you get older, do you get more selfish?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "They're too emotionally needy?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "The drama queens?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "But you've learned the power of saying no?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "And is there something you have to learn with time, do you think?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I -- yes, I felt love from them.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you feel real love from them or not?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "URNETT: Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Did she really?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Love it.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Well, that's just great, isn't it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Exactly, exactly.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Why should it always be the older guy with a younger woman?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "But when you look back, you've never felt that fame itself has had any kind of corrosive impact on your life?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "URNETT: No, also I'm not -- I don't think even if I were around today and this was my time to be on television, I don't think I would be pursued as much.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "That wasn't like it in your day, was it?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Can you relate to that?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "The trick was I got her into rehab before she was going to turn 18.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What was the trick, you think?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "That's harder.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Is it harder when you've got somebody like Charlie who's 50 now?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "It's not supposed to be that way, is it?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I live with it every day.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Or do you live with it every day?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Did you feel that, devastating though it was that she died in her late 30s, that actually because of the way she turned her life around in her teens, you kind of got possibly 20 more years than you may have done, had she continued down the early route?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I think I have the same outlook I had before.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Did you change your outlook on life?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I'm doing OK.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "And how are you finding that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I don't want to say yet.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What kind of book is it?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "They didn't want to do it and they didn't think we'd run past even a half a season.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "They didn't really want to do it?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "When they renewed us.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "This was going to be big?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Was it controlled chaos?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "No, he said his wife's sister has a weak chin and he wanted to know what I went through.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Did he have it done?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Your weak bladder cost you possibly another three hours of Marlon Brando?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Oh yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Was that fun for you?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "That's --", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Who were the greatest stars of them all?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "It's pretty good, actually.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "How is her voice these days?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "They've both quite rugged chaps.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "I mean, what is not to love?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "I don't try to, but I'm lucky to have them around.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "But have you always tried to surround yourself with funny people too?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Oh, I think.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "Is it a particular genius, that, to be a great gag merchant?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "URNETT: I think it was probably when I lost out on a show that I was auditioning for.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "I want you to tell me, what's the moment you would relive if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "I'll try.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Can you still do it?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110421pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "Is that in the pipeline?", "qSentId": 786}]